You can automate a couple of tasks in the DevOps
using the Python and the Go language.
Let's see how we can do that.
So here we're going to open up our editor,
and in the editor you can see that I have written
one list.py that is a Python file.
I can run this file, and this will give me the list of all the clusters.
Similarly, I can write this automation script even in the Go language as well.
What you need to do is whenever somebody asks you to
list out all the names of the clusters,
now you don't have to go and manually do it.
You can just run the script, and this will give you all the information.
You just open the terminal and write command like python
list.py. And this automation command is going to run and give me
the list of all the clusters available.
So similarly, you can do it with the Go language as well.
So you can do a couple of automation into your Google
DevOps by using this Python and Go scripts.
I have attached all those scripts as a part of this
module so that you can go through it.